Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
A glittering Raana short sword
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 8
Wandering
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
3 Hours Later
Wandering
Dreamlord
But
Monster: Tin Knight
Dreamlord:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hEmbryo
Skill Trees: Heavy Knight
Remaining Skill Points: 9
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 27
Shield Bash skill has been acquired
Shield Bash [Common Skill]
Push an enemy with a shield and knock them back
Disarm
Rampart Reflection
Repair
Earth Magic Stone Patchwork Bear
Spend MP to fire countless needles of earth
Sylph Cutter
Status Effect
Stunned